[music]
on the topics.
I hope you are well.  I currently have
another vlog about going to
Kosovo.  You will take
Sabrina and I with you, as always, before I go
to Kosovo, and you will also do some things
that I am doing.  We're leaving, we're taking you
with us now, as always, I'll take you
with me later, bye, so now we're going to pick up Sabrin, we're getting
ready, airport direction [music] we're
ready, people
[music]
Kosovo Kosovo We're
going to pick up Sabrin from work,
airport direction, balloon balloon,
Pristina, I couldn't find a car,
rent a car, stuff, there's nothing in a car, I don't know what you're doing,
full full full, Kosovo, I couldn't find a car, we'll find a car, I'll take it to the car, it's currently full,
nobody's
found,
implut
music
[music]
people here, here, I'm nervous,
very nervous, I've got two more kilos,
and I have to take out my stuff, where
have you reserved the car to pick me up in
order, my friend didn't say hello, was
it my mistake, there's a
lot of things, I notified you too late, I didn't
know, I'll leave for next
time, I'll go ahead, but I don't
Believe me, there are 30 people left, not
one of them has been a disaster this season,
but for another time, I go to my friend
and greet him from the bottom of my heart, so
late, I wish he had
Skat,
so let's greet Arton.  Arton
greets you,
so that
you too can have [music] of
[song]
not Prizren, who is well prepared
[music]
candidate.
Here, the sea is
from Peja tomorrow, it opens in Prizren, from
Prizren it opens in Peja, and the
direction to Switzerland, the direction to the sea,
because the door here is not closed, because the sea has no
stress, fill it up
as much as you want, and for those mornings I'm going
to Switzerland and from there to the sea.  It
's good to come here when it's not the season,
where is the mid-season? How are you
liking the village here, my village, I
'll report it. Look at what village you're in. This is a big,
You have come to Kosovo,
but Peja is
good, you guys have come,
amen n amen.  We are tired.  We're a little tired
.  Yes, you are tired.  Now we have to call it a
wedding with
kismet.
Are they good?  Sabin
Nutada
Sali,
people, we had a good time in Pejë.
The pool is ready.  I'll have to shoot it later, but this
car doesn't know
,
I don't even know how I got it.   Come on, let's just have a
little fun for now.
Disaster
after that, thank God.  But now
that I'm here, I haven't used it.   It's no
use here.  This is the brandy this friend of the
father is cheerful now like the ladies that the sound is fresh
or hey that collector come on let's
stay a little and like this once I got
bored
for goodness walk with the shadow tarak had been
ready hla e
chârta what are you doing
who wants to come in here Forget
we are with family all are tired they are not talking they are not
enjoying without me and there is no sale do you
know
[laughter]
don't leave it
wow [music] Come on
[song]
relax with my brother
[music]
[music][song]
ma
[laughter]
on a youtube channel
geng these others are waiting for us there we are
never going together
with my sister Mustafa
kollamaq
kallamaq Hoq yes yes
with my voice longing for pej that pejë
aj aj aj aj aj for
mc
aura aura aura aura leo
so
come on come on come with me come so
the whole troope here
drinks
How much light game
when the
topics
[laughter] are
true.
Okay, I'm planning for tomorrow
because you're only
11 okay after 12 you have your birthday
and for tomorrow kismet I want to have a
good one look at the sahi a do you see do you have sahi I want to have a
good Na to bring you pan
as h on the head the head is written a calf I want to
cut for you
with some grell
h
and I want to sing for
Anxhelina tonight because we don't have a singer
praise you said the meat you bought come on I'm
leaving koll mau home.  Let's
go.  Bye.   I'm not adding this because I didn't give it to him
.   You
left it to the village of
Prizren, Xebi, Saranda, Sabri.  I need to pay
another visit soon, as I'm already there
.
Those who are asleep are not waking up, brother.  We are getting up
.  They're trying to get out a little and
make the most of these days.
Tonight, it rained with Sebi, Saranda
and Sabrina.  We are eating something that
our tribe has taken from us.
And for
now, heading towards Peja, because the music is waiting for us
tonight, it seems to me that it's mega trom
Prizren, my trum
k movie,
film, chicken, chicken,
ferik, Paume,
sheni, blade,
special ritimi, half a chicken, I had given it.   No, no, there are
mega drugs
.
What's your problem?  Yes, one night
[music]
you are beautiful, but when you are up in the
[music] sky you are a pore.  [song]
I wanted [music] my when I dance
in the night [music] you are
beautiful
[music]
for father and mother [song]
with the gerbet
I am I know about Kosovo [song]
in the
gerbet now I am I am [music]
father mother to [song] I live my heart
fills [music]
with the baj for Kosovo has taken now the gerbet
I am a
wedding
but since we don't have a wedding tonight we have come on
Aisori
tonight we have a wedding
everyone is singing [laughter]
I forgive you for your mistakes
and you [song] forgive me well
[music]
We prepared it like this for
Sebi's birthday and the night of the kanajeg a little for
fun I had an idea and we are doing it with
music I have my blessing with the attitude
that I greet you very much thank you very much
except with good things the chicks are getting ready.  I almost ordered
a sacrifice.  We have a grill to
tell you,
even once a year, good bye, and so I greet you from the heart, Jenif,
find it [music], I'll leave it, I'll leave it,
memory
[music], come on
Sabria,
oh marshal, come on, it's useless
[music][song] marshal,
you raised the
debt [song][music]
glory
fi
çong debt [music][song] it
was debt
[song][music]
many congratulations to you many congratulations [song]
to you many congratulations many [music] congratulations
many congratulations to you [music]
fryashen.
Bravo,
bravo, bravo, bravo,
bravo.  Congratulations, congratulations.
And the best thing, my friend, is that [music] is so
beautiful.
[music]
About [song]
good friend, there is [music] one
[song]
that knows
[music]
that I can do anything [music]
with a bard, I want to
be [music] I am for this one
who made me happy,
bravo,
come on, Valbona, come on
[music]
[song] let's wish her [music]
[song]
[music]
For good sister, for good girl
[music] let's be happy
[song]
oh come on [music]
let's wish her [music] my sister [music] Oh, that
you [music] wish her [music] oh.  [song]
Bravo sister, I had no
problem at all,
all the family, the verse is
good, you are happy,
you are happy, so it seems to me
that it is super, it is good   Okay,
bro.  Come on, sisters.
Well done, well done.   Yes, you
should leave it alone,
this one is better
than the other one there
.   Here
.
[laughter]
Leon come on insall amen
insallah
frank frank a music
to music sp yes yes
[ __ ] but we all make a
good picture
all Prizren
Piran Piran everyone everyone
with my dan we are
ready we
are ready
come on I hope we will call you yes
as a promo my time good
morning
[music]
Shë e
çon tren [music] piss are you
ready Albanian you for me
for what are you ready yes he with
b me call as for e you have call you
are call call
call that every time be
z
ohem
[music]
oh let's go
[music] [music]
[music]
that
[song] This [music]
[music]
we're done
fix
Come on
I'm already since last time a
we had a good time even
very good
like you [ __ ] sh
with makeup
dunkling nik We took
the whole family complete mom bought a
birthday thank you mom
and yes take me back tomorrow I'll go back
to Switzerland yes
and on the same evening there is still a
surprise the drive we fly We
actually always fly, but
this time must  we drive and I
also take my nicest car we drive to
Kotas
France Kotasop
can Monaco I'm excited I
actually like the French side
not at all France
Let see
let's go get
these nus
Lori
yes update
for example
fly back
dr
also direction to Switzerland I'm glad we have to
rest a bit we have to follow Brendon
Brendon hello We
also have to go back home, but
tomorrow morning we have to leave Kotas zy
so little
thanks aj tashu.
Hey people, I hope you are well,
that you are healthy
with the grace of God.  I, Sabria, have
returned to Switzerland.  And tonight we are going on
vacation.  We are going to the sea, we are going
to France.  Apartment with Cannes in a
good location Santrope Monaco.  Let's see if it's
good or not.  No, we take it with us as always, before we leave, we're going to change
cars.  Here we are going by jeep, we are
going by another car.  I'm drinking it there
heading to France, the vlog in Kosovo is
done.  I hope you liked it a lot.   But now he took you with him to the Khan
.  That
's another vlog.  I
greet you from the bottom of my heart, as always, Sabri.